If I miss my curfew,
Father will yell at me again!
Ow...
Are you okay?
Y-Yes... I think I just
sprained it a little...
Don't move.
What in the...?
Try standing up.
--It doesn't hurt.
--That's good.
Ah, I can put my shoes on myself...
There you go.
What did you do? Was that
some trick? Or magic?
Bye.
Please wait!
What's your name?
I'm Brad.
Brad...
Can we meet again?
Sorry!
Do you understand me, Angelina?!
I forbid you to see that man anymore!
Why?! Brad is such a good person!
I don't care. You are not to meet him!
And you'll stay in this room until
you promise me that you won't!
This is for your own good.
I'm counting on you.
Understood, sir.
Brad...
This darn thing!
Hey, give it a rest.
You can mess around
with that broken TV all day,
but it's not like some genie's gonna
pop out and grant you three wishes.
And today is the final episode...
Well, that's too bad.
Me, I'm bummed too, 'cuz
my nap's been interrupted.
Go and buy a new one now!
If I had the cash...
How in the world do you blow
through all your money so fast?!
I got that demonic woman
collecting loans from me,
and a tightfisted slave-driver
for an agent...
Who's tightfisted?
What's up? Here with some more
jobs that won't make me any money?
Nope. I only bring jobs that pay out.
On the condition that they're done right...
Hey, Morrison. Can you fix a TV?
A TV?
It's broke, and today's the last
episode of "Bolero in Spring"!
You got your car here today, Morrison?
Yeah.
I'll take the job if you let me
get some sleep in it on the way.
I've been losing sleep due to that broken TV.
Let's get going already.
I don't care where to, as long as I don't
have to hear any whining about that TV...
Good day, Miss.
You're not going to fix the TV, Morrison?
You can have Dante buy you one
with the money he makes from this job.
Wait, Morrison!
That won't be in time for the last
episode of "Bolero in Spring"!
Hey! You jerks!
Miss, your meal is ready.
I don't want to eat.
Please Miss... If you don't, I'll
be in trouble with your father.
This is a pretty swank pad.
What kind of racket does he run
to afford something like this?
He's the mayor of Capulet City.
Hello, sorry I'm late. That meeting
dragged out longer than I thought it would...
Thanks for coming. I'm Mike Hagel.
I'm Morrison.
Nice to meet you.
Let's skip the formalities, and get down
to business before I fall asleep again.
Huh?
You got my word. He's good...
Even if he is a little
rough around the edges.
I want this man killed.
Please... Kill him.
I've got a daughter, my only child.
Her name is Angelina.
My wife died a long time ago, and since then
I've raised my little darling all on my own.
My daughter means everything to me.
And this Brad guy is planning on taking my
daughter away from this town and from me!
I won't allow this worthless drifter to just run
off with my daughter because he feels like it.
And so you want me to kill him?
Well, that sure makes for a grand story...
Turn it into a soap opera
and Patty would love it.
Um...
Miss.
I think I should at least be
able to use the washroom alone.
Did you know that there's some murderer
on the loose in Capulet City recently?
It's been all over the news.
My TV's broke, remember?
Oh yeah...
At any rate, there have been such incidents.
This is it.
It's so gruesome, there are even some
people saying that the culprit isn't human.
Not human?
These random assaults started happening right
around the time that this Brad guy showed up.
So you're saying that this "Brad"
isn't just a murderer, but a devil?
That's ridiculous.
I saw it with my own eyes.
There's no doubt about it. He's a devil!
Right up your alley, don't you think?
I'm begging you! Kill this Brad!
Brad...
Brad!
Please! Let's run away together!
What's wrong all of a sudden?
Try to calm yourself down
and tell me what's going on.
I think my father has hired someone...
to kill you!
Kill me?
But why?
Because of your strange power!
My father thinks you're a devil!
Does he now...
Let's run away together!
Angelina...
I'm sorry, but I can't let you
get wrapped up in all of this.
But I...
Don't worry about me, Angelina.
I'll be all right.
Someday your father will understand, too.
But...
You should be going home.
I'm glad I could see you.
Mind if a grab a seat?
Huh?
Yeah, go right ahead.
I'll take a beer. And a pizza.
Any kind, as long as there are no olives.
Don't mind me. Go about your reading.
Oh, thanks...
What? You still can't find Angelina?!
Don't even think about
coming back here until you do!
Is she at that guy's place again?!
Sir, my apologies.
This is all because I took my eyes off her...
Miss!
Father...
Do you understand me?!
From now on your meals
will be brought to your room,
and you'll be watched everywhere you go!
Brad...
What's this book you're all into?
It's a romance novel.
Hmmm... any good?
Yeah, really good.
One person's love for
another is a wonderful thing.
True love is a thing of beauty!
Do you find that strange?
--No.
--One beer.
Took long enough for
just a beer... And my pizza?
They're making it now.
Damn...
--Cheers.
--Uh, yeah, cheers.
By the way, you seem kind
of like a drifter...
Where are you from?
You don't have to answer
that if you don't want to.
Well, I'm going to be on my way.
Here's your pizza. Sorry to keep you waiting.
Hey, there's olives on this thing.
Of course there are.
Dammit.
They say the gate will open tonight!
Will it, now?
But having to leave the human
world is kind of a shame...
So you really were the one responsible
for that string of murders?
I'm very fond of the blood of the living...
Who's there?!
Did you follow me?
Eating a large pizza in five minutes
is a new personal record for me.
Don't you mess with me!
That's some handshake.
You're as strong as I'd heard.
You make it sound like you know who I am.
I've been in the living
world for a month now.
I've heard the rumors about
Dante, "The Devil Hunter."
So I guess I can take that as a
confession that you're not human, right?
Yes.
Well, then I guess you've got no objections.
Correct. I don't imagine I could escape you.
But there's just one thing I have to ask.
What's that?
I heard that you're a half-breed...
Born from the union of a human and a devil.
If that's so, can you tell me...
were your parents in love?
Was there love between human and devil?
Who knows?
One always hears stories about married couples
who look like they were made for each other,
but whose hearts are really cold as ice.
That's not what...
But, to me it looked as if they truly loved
one another from the bottom of their hearts.
Really?
Was that all you wanted to say?
Yeah.
I thought you might try to
pull a surprise attack on me.
I know I can't defeat you.
You're kind of a wimp for being a devil...
Even though I am a devil,
there's no way I could fight you.
Besides, my role here is finished.
Finished?
Tonight, my master from the
demon world will come to this world.
A certain human summoned me
here to make those preparations.
Why are you telling me this?
Maybe because I want you
to put an end to it...
My master's greedy.
I'm sure he'll try to
devour this entire city.
That café with the wonderful coffee...
And the hill with such a
beautiful view of the setting sun...
Everything...
And Angelina too?
What should I do? I don't want to lose her...
She was so kind to me.
I've always been treated so
cruelly in the demon world,
but she'd smile at me.
I don't even want to think about
the possibility of her being devoured.
But... I'm a devil.
I don't have the power to defy my master.
It's true, you're pretty
pathetic... for a devil.
But if you're capable of that much love for
Angelina, you'll be able to live as a human.
A human? Me?
--Take me there.
--Huh?
To the gate that is tied to the demon world.
Father?
Father?! What happened?!
Father!
Father?!
Father! Father!
Hang on, Father!
Don't move.
If you had just stayed in
your room like a good girl,
you could have died
without having to feel fear...
Y-You... Why would you
do something like this?
Soon, a powerful devil will be summoned
to this city by the ritual I have performed.
Together we shall destroy this world!
Dante!
Sorry. I guess I knocked a little too hard...
I had a bad feeling about you from
the moment I saw you with the mayor.
But you're too late!
Angelina!
Brad!
Sir, hang in there!
Brad! Do you plan to betray Belphagor?!
You're already too late!
Belphagor will be here soon!
I'm sure it must have
been a long, hard journey...
Too bad entry here is restricted.
Sorry, but I'm going to
have to ask you to leave!
Angelina!
Father!
What is this...?
Don't try to speak, Father.
Brad, please!
Okay. I've never tried it on a wound
as serious as this, but I'll try my best.
What... do you think
you're doing to me... you devil...
Do you think... that by doing this for me...
I'm going to allow you to... see my daughter?
Father!
Don't worry yourself.
That is not what I'm thinking.
No, I'm doing this simply because
I don't want to see Angelina sad.
Mr. Mayor, sorry, but it doesn't look like
I'm going to be able to grant your request.
Brad understands love.
He'll make it just fine as a human.
And the only things I
can exterminate are devils.
Hey Morrison, haven't you got it fixed yet?
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
How much longer am I going to have to wait?!
Just wait a little bit longer, okay, Miss?
By the way, Dante...
It's a nice story about how those
two finally got her dad's approval.
But I don't see how your passing up on
the money should result in my fixing this TV...
Less talking and more fixing!
My afternoon soap opera's about to start!
Yes, Ma'am....
You fixed it!
I'll deduct my repair fees
from your next payment.
Whatever...
Good grief.
At this rate you'll never get your debt paid
off, no matter how many good jobs I bring you.
But you seem happy, Dante...
Even though you usually do nothing but
complain when you don't get your money...
Every now and then there are days like this.
I sure hope those two
will be happy, don't you?
I've always had pretty bad luck with women.
I'd be lucky if they'd just beat me up.
But they'd also do things like stick swords
in my stomach, and shoot me in the forehead...
If I wasn't who I am, I'd
probably be dead. Damn...
And what's more, the women
that do those things
are the very women I just can't
seem to boot out of my life.
I wonder when my luck
with women will improve...